<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipiverse</string>
    <string name="web_client_id">979946881174-n036bffq9p9pa0i4n4tmflhfdbkcrns3.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">\nLast Updated: 03/11/2024\n\nWelcome to RECIPIVERSE! By signing up, accessing, or using our app, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms and Conditions (hereinafter referred to as “Terms”). These Terms govern your use of the RECIPIVERSE platform, a social network for food enthusiasts to share recipes, food images, videos, and text posts. If you disagree with any part of these Terms, you should refrain from using the RECIPIVERSE app.\n\n 1. Acceptance of Terms\n\nBy creating an account, you signify your agreement to these Terms and our Privacy Policy. If you are using the platform on behalf of an organization, you represent that you have the authority to accept these Terms on behalf of that organization.\n\n 2. Account Registration and Security\n\n- Account Requirements: To access RECIPIVERSE, you must be at least 13 years old (or meet the minimum age of digital consent in your country).\n- Accuracy of Information: You agree to provide accurate, current, and complete information during registration. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account password.\n- Account Security: You are responsible for all activities under your account. Notify RECIPIVERSE immediately of any unauthorized use of your account.\n\n 3. User-Generated Content\n\n 3.1 Ownership and Rights\n- By posting or sharing content on RECIPIVERSE, including text, images, and videos (collectively “Content”), you retain ownership of any intellectual property rights in that Content.\n- You grant RECIPIVERSE a non-exclusive, transferable, sublicensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use, distribute, modify, display, and perform your Content in connection with operating, promoting, and improving the platform.\n\n 3.2 Content Guidelines\n- Content should be food-related, respectful, and not offensive.\n- Prohibited Content includes but is not limited to:\n    - Inappropriate or Obscene Content: Includes any nudity, pornographic, or explicit content.\n    - Violent or Hateful Content: No threatening, abusive, harassing, or discriminatory material.\n    - Illegal Content: Content promoting illegal activities or substances.\n    - Misinformation: Do not share false information regarding health, food safety, or nutritional information.\n\n 3.3 Responsibility for Content\nYou acknowledge that you are solely responsible for your Content and any consequences of posting it. RECIPIVERSE reserves the right to remove any Content that violates these Terms.\n\n 4. Community Conduct\n\n- Respectful Interactions: Engage with others respectfully. Harassment, bullying, hate speech, and any conduct that creates a hostile environment is prohibited.\n- No Spam or Bots: Automated accounts, spam, or misleading engagements are not allowed.\n- Reporting Violations: You can report users or content that violate these Terms. RECIPIVERSE may review and take appropriate action.\n\n 5. Privacy and Data Use\n\nYour privacy is important to us. Please review our Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use, and disclose information about you.\n\n 5.1 User Data\n- Data Collection: We may collect data you provide, such as profile information and activity data, for account setup and feature use.\n- Third-Party Services: RECIPIVERSE may use third-party services to improve the platform’s functionality. By using RECIPIVERSE, you agree to share certain data as described in our Privacy Policy.\n\n 6. Content Moderation\n\nWe strive to provide a safe and positive environment. However, RECIPIVERSE is not responsible for user-posted Content. We reserve the right but are not obligated, to monitor, modify, or remove any Content for any reason, including violation of these Terms.\n\n 7. Intellectual Property Rights\n\nAll intellectual property rights on the platform, including software, branding, and design elements, are owned by RECIPIVERSE. You may not copy, modify, distribute, or otherwise use our intellectual property without prior written consent.\n\n 8. Disclaimer of Warranties\n\nRECIPIVERSE is provided on an “as-is” and “as-available” basis. We do not guarantee the platform will be error-free, secure, or available at all times.\n\n- No Warranties: We disclaim all warranties of any kind, express or implied, regarding the platform’s operation or availability.\n- Third-Party Content: We are not responsible for any third-party websites or resources linked on the platform.\n\n 9. Limitation of Liability\n\nTo the fullest extent permitted by law, RECIPIVERSE and its affiliates will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages resulting from your use or inability to use the platform.\n\n 10. Indemnification\n\nYou agree to indemnify and hold RECIPIVERSE, its affiliates, and their respective officers, directors, employees, and agents harmless from any claims, damages, or expenses arising from your use of the platform or breach of these Terms.\n\n 11. Changes to Terms\n\nRECIPIVERSE reserves the right to modify these Terms at any time. Any changes will be posted within the app, and your continued use of the platform will indicate acceptance of the revised Terms.\n\n 12. Termination of Use\n\nWe reserve the right to suspend or terminate your account at our sole discretion if you violate these Terms or engage in unlawful or harmful behavior on the platform.\n\n 13. Governing Law\n\nThese Terms are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of United Kingdom. You agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in United Kingdom.\n\n## 14. Contact Us\n\nFor questions or feedback regarding these Terms, please contact us at contact@recipiverse.com.\n\n--- \n\nEnd of Terms and Conditions\n</string>

</resources>